KEVIN MORRISON

A Nurse Practitioner with IO-*-years of experience delivering mental health treatments for patients suffering from depression and anxiety disorders. A proven track record of diagnosing disorders and identifying ideal medications to improve quality of life,

123 Pine Brook Dr, Miami, FL 12345 kevi n mo rri son@exam ple.com {123) 456-7890 LinkedIn | Portfolio

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NURSE PRACTITIONER

Better Help, Miami, FL July 2016 - Present

NURSE PRACTITIONER

Life Stance, Miami, FL June2013-July 2016

- Deliver mental health services to patients suffering from a wide range of disorders, evaluate symptoms and family histories, develop treatment plans, prescribe medications, and successfully reduced anxiety and depression symptoms
- ♦ Provide em patheti c care to pati ents, build positive I ong-term relati on s h i ps, a nd provide resources related to mental health counseling services
- Delivered mental health treatment and services to 40+ active patients, analyzed medical histories, and collaborated with patients to develop treatment plans in alignment with long-term health goals
- Monitored medication side effects to ensure patient safety over the course of treatment, adjusted doses, and successfully reduced depression and anxiety levels

EDUCATION

Master of Science (B.S.) Nursing University of Florida, Gainesville, FL September 2011 - June 2013

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Nursing University of Florida, Gainesville, FL September 2007 - June 2011

KEY SKILLS

- Mental Health Treatment
- Medication Management
- ♦ Evidence-Based Treatment Plans
- Patient Education
- ♦ Empathetic Care

CERTIFICATIONS

- Psychiatric-Mental Health Nurse Practitioner (PMHNP), 2013
- Family Nurse Practitioner
 Certification, American Academy of Nurse Practitioners, 2013